tsbmen.com 2015-06-09

# | Articles of Style

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally identifiable information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as used in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

****What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app? When and why is it collected?  
****

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience. We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter and/or enter information (ie: for a giveaway) on our site.

****How do we use your information?  
****

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication in order to make improvements to the site, better handle your customer service requests, and send periodic emails regarding the site.

****Do we use ‘cookies’?  
****

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer a better site experience as we grow. Cookies are also used to keep track of advertisements on the site.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser’s settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser’s Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

****Third Party Disclosure  
****

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

****Google  
****

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles – https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. We use Google AdSense Advertising and Doubleclick for Publishers on our website.

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google, use first-party cookies (ie: Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (ie: DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.. Users may opt out of the use of the Doubleclick cookie by visiting https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en .

****California Online Privacy Protection Act  
****

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. – See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

**  
** Users can visit our site anonymously. Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page, or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’, and can be easily be found on the page specified above. Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

****COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)  
****

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation’s consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online. We do not specifically market to children under 13.

****Contacting Us  
****

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the link in the header above.
